<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestX</string>

    <string name="welcome_title">Welcome to STOP</string>
    <string name="welcome_details">STOP is designed for Parkinson\'s patients for tracking motor abilities and increasing medication adherence.\n\nThe motor functionalities are estimated with a ball game. The goal of the game is to keep the red ball motionless in the center of the inner black circle by balancing the device horizontally on the palm of the hand. The game success is evaluated using 0 (min) - 100 (max) scale. In addition the user is asked to record the medication taking time to the journal. The research will use the collected information for searching correlation between motor functionalities and medication effectiveness.\n\nSTOP application sends notifications about the game and medication recording four times per day. Once per day user is asked to evaluate the level of symptoms.</string>
    <string name="consent_details">The University of Oulu (Finland) and the University of Manchester (UK) are using this application to better understand Parkinson’s medication adherence and effectiveness via gamification and medication logs. By installing and agreeing to this consent, you effectively become a participant to our joint research effort. If you disagree, you may still use the application without any data sharing.\n\n<b>Data Collection</b>\n- Your answers to the initial Parkinson’s patient profile questions\n- Accelerometer, gyroscope, orientation data from the phone ONLY during game sessions of our STOP game\n- Your medication taking times\n- Application stability data collected via Google Analytics (crashes)\n\n<b>Security and Privacy</b>\nHIPAA and GDPR compliant: the encrypted data is securely sent to our server in Oulu for further analysis on a regular basis over WiFi. No personal identifiers are collected. Personalisable name for a randomly assigned UUID. If withdrawn from data collection, the server data is erased.</string>
    <string name="consent_title">Research consent</string>

    <string name="btn_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="btn_next">Next</string>

    <string name="provider_game_label">STOP application data</string>
</resources>
